<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dietary Fiber on Craigccfl</title>
    <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/tags/dietary-fiber/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dietary Fiber on Craigccfl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 08:38:47 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.craigccfl.com/tags/dietary-fiber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven important reasons not to eat wheat</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/7reasons-wheat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 08:38:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/7reasons-wheat/</guid>
      <description>Eating whole grain breads to improve your health and increase fiber? Maybe it is not such a great idea. If it is processed food, it probably has wheat or a wheat by-product in the ingredients. Wheat is subsidized by our government, it&amp;rsquo;s cheap and very profitable for food companies. There&amp;rsquo;s many problems stemming from wheat products, detailed in the book Grain Brain (see books category). Dr Ken Berry has hundreds of YouTube videos posted online designed to help people improve their health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiber is not necessarily beneficial for health</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/fiber/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/fiber/</guid>
      <description>Carbohydrates are not a necessary nutrient for human health and fiber, both insoluble and soluble, are carbohydrates. There is no clinical data substantiating our health is dependent upon our intake of fiber. There is a clinical study in the publications section of this site discussing improved digestion when fiber is removed and Dr. Paul Saladino sums up the subject very well in the linked YouTube video.
There’s several researchers and medical doctors that are not buying into the fiber crap, (pardon the pun).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>