<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>USDA Guidelines on Craigccfl</title>
    <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/tags/usda-guidelines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in USDA Guidelines on Craigccfl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 08:52:24 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.craigccfl.com/tags/usda-guidelines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/dgac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 08:52:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/dgac/</guid>
      <description>We’ll another episode from the Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee (DGAC) now recommending Americans restrict their saturated fat from 10% to 7%. This flies in the face of clinical research and hundreds of thousands anecdotal studies the last 5-years definitively showing the damage excessive carbohydrates cause liver, kidney, heart and brain damage.
Think about it, we’re not good at making energy from protein, the process of converting protein to energy is highly inefficient; our protein requirement is for rebuilding tissue, not energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USDA Guidelines; Fact or Fiction</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/usda-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 07:54:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/usda-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Dietary Guidelines 2015-20
The nation&amp;rsquo;s experts look at the best available science (or do they) to determine for the masses the best dietary practices for a healthy life. Their findings are found with facts, not conjecture, for they are the world&amp;rsquo;s experts. Is this how things really work? The Dietary Guideline for Americans (DGA) are all the proven facts? The decision makers in the DGA do not have any conflicts of interest, political bias, secret agendas?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>