<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" 
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" 
  xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Craigccfl</title>
    <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Craigccfl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 08:59:23 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://craigccfl.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    

      
      <item>
        <title>Low cholesterol increases all cause mortality</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/cholesterol_longivity/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 08:59:23 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 08:59:23 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/cholesterol_longivity/</guid>
        <description>Want a healthy brain when older, ditch the statins and change your diet. The Cholesterol and all-cause mortality in elderly people from the
Honolulu Heart Program: a cohort study is just an association; however, the science behind Ancel Keys&amp;rsquo; saturated fat &amp;amp; cholesterol contributing to heart disease is also an association study, one that was manipulated to reveal a bias result Resources here Scientist are perplexed with the results of the Cholesterol and all-cause mortality study.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/cholesterol.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Cholesterol</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Nutritional Confusion</category>
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Carnivore Eating</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/carivore/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 13:07:05 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 13:07:05 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/carivore/</guid>
        <description>The ultimate way to eat zero carb. Most people end up on a carnivore diet by going through a process, they generally start out with Paleo then move to low-carb high-fat (LCHF) then many of us spend time doing the ketogenic diet. Usually, just out of curiosity, some of us move into a carnivore diet. IMO, it never hurts to try something for a couple months just to see how you feel (N=1).</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.comimages/posts/ribeye.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Carnivore</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Red Meat</category>
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Is eating chicken healthy?</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/reducingfats/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 11:06:07 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 11:06:07 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/reducingfats/</guid>
        <description>Reducing saturated fats as suggested by our USDA, is very bad advice. They got it all wrong when they started promoting vegetable oils to replace saturated fats. Conventional wisdom suggests eating polyunsaturated fatty acid (PUFA) oils are healthier for our heart, despite interventional studies dating back to the 60s proving this advice is misleading. We consume more PUFAs today, yet the metabolic health of our society is rapidly declining each decade.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/Chicken1.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Oxidized Oils</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Vegetable &amp; Seed Oils</category>
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Nutritional Confusion</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Videos</category>
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Learn how to burn fat, keeping it simple (KIS)</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/kis/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 15:29:10 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 15:29:10 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/kis/</guid>
        <description>Dr. Ken Berry, &amp;ldquo;Suffering from Dunlaps disease, follow these instructions.&amp;rdquo; What&amp;rsquo;s Dunlaps disease? It&amp;rsquo;s when the belly done lops over the belt holding up your pants. Coming to the realization this site has a lot of postings debunking mainstream nutritional guidance and not much instruction written in keep it simple (KIS) format, decided to post something different called, Simple steps for becoming fat adapted. The reason for this specific guidance is based on N=1 and what I&amp;rsquo;ve seen and heard thousands of others accomplish by taking some of these steps.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/familyguy.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Burn body fat</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Simple Steps</category>
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Nutritional Confusion</category>
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Humans are fat hunters</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/homininbrains/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 16:43:28 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 16:43:28 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/homininbrains/</guid>
        <description>Our nutritional needs have not changed. Scientist are aware of the fact, species cannot have a large digestive system and a large brain. There is only so much energy to distribute, it either goes to the brain or to the digestive system. Animals either need a large stomach and intestine to extract energy from low caloric plant foods or have an increase in intelligence from eating dense nutrient bio-available foods usually derived from consuming animals.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/homo-habilis.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Hominin Brains</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Fat Hunters</category>
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Intermittent Fasting</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/intermittent-fasting/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 18:08:23 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 18:08:23 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/intermittent-fasting/</guid>
        <description>Never skip a meal - - Right? People that know me, especially while traveling for work, mention that I eat like a snake. When I do eat, it&amp;rsquo;s a lot and when I&amp;rsquo;m not eating, it can be for a few days. This is what&amp;rsquo;s nice about being fat adapted, if there&amp;rsquo;s nothing healthy to eat, which there rarely is when traveling, it&amp;rsquo;s not a problem to skip a few meals: It&amp;rsquo;s called not being a slave to food.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/fasting.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Fasting</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Fasting</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Meats Justified</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/tmao/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 11:24:03 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 11:24:03 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/tmao/</guid>
        <description>TMAO, no correlation to atherosclerosis. This is a technical paper for those who have delved into some of the scientific discussions regarding over activation of human growth hormone and its relationship with long-term health. The consensuses (beliefs) states over activation of metabolite trimethylamine-N-oxide (TMAO), creates excessive cellular oxidation leading to atherosclerosis, and diets high in choline (meat) cause over activation of TMAO. This is the science used by many who recommend limiting protein to an absolute minimum, usually 20% or less.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/4-steaks.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Red Meat</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Nutritional Confusion</category>
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Seven important reasons not to eat wheat</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/7reasons-wheat/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 08:38:47 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 08:38:47 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/7reasons-wheat/</guid>
        <description>Eating whole grain breads to improve your health and increase fiber? Maybe it is not such a great idea. If it is processed food, it probably has wheat or a wheat by-product in the ingredients. Wheat is subsidized by our government, it&amp;rsquo;s cheap and very profitable for food companies. There&amp;rsquo;s many problems stemming from wheat products, detailed in the book Grain Brain (see books category). Dr Ken Berry has hundreds of YouTube videos posted online designed to help people improve their health.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/ken-berry.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Wheat</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Dietary Fiber</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Videos</category>
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Nutritional Confusion</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Videos</category>
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/dgac/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 08:52:24 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 08:52:24 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/dgac/</guid>
        <description>Do not pay attention to the recommendations of the DGAC, if you want to be healthy. We’ll another episode from the Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee (DGAC) now recommending Americans restrict their saturated fat from 10% to 7%. This flies in the face of clinical research and hundreds of thousands anecdotal studies the last 5-years definitively showing the damage excessive carbohydrates cause liver, kidney, heart and brain damage.
Think about it, we’re not good at making energy from protein, the process of converting protein to energy is highly inefficient; our protein requirement is for rebuilding tissue, not energy.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/nina.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>USDA Guidelines</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Nutritional Confusion</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>COVID-19</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/covid19/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 05:15:49 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 05:15:49 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/covid19/</guid>
        <description>Brief look at nutrition&amp;rsquo;s role in the complications many endure when infected with COVID-19. Mainstream news seems to agree on one thing, the death toll brought about due to COVID-19 is disproportionally affecting those with hypertension, diabetes, liver disease, smokers &amp;amp; the obese. Additional studies are noting other factors such as low vitamin D, zinc and other mineral deficiencies. On the surface, most think the metabolic disorders are related to aging in general; however, researchers and some doctors are starting to publish papers addressing the real elephant in the room, our Standard American diet (SAD).</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/COVID19.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>COVID-19</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Videos</category>
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Nutritional Confusion</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Is salting our food bad for us?</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/salt_bad/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 10:59:06 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 10:59:06 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/salt_bad/</guid>
        <description>Salt is essential for life. Our experts often advise us to restrict salt intake, based on what, faulty science? The answer to this question is yes, faulty science. Complications from insufficient salt intake are far worse than consuming excessive salt. The human body easily regulates excessive salt, with no side effects. The body cannot deal with a lack of salt in our systems. Low salt intake exacerbates insulin resistance, heart palpitations, dysfunctions in the nervous systems, headaches, increases hunger, etc.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/salt.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Salt Intake</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Videos</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Low carb &amp; keto what about cholesterol </title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/cholesterol2/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 18:21:49 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 18:21:49 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/cholesterol2/</guid>
        <description>High LDL is also associated with longevity. What I&amp;rsquo;ve Learned
This content creator puts out some good research pertaining to new science developments in the field of nutrition. Cholesterol is a hot topic, one of the major points of the nay sayers when discussing a diet low in carbs, high in saturated fats. Eating LCHF may increase your cholesterol; however, there&amp;rsquo;s much more to cholesterol than what we&amp;rsquo;ve been told.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/time_cholesterol.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Cholesterol</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Videos</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Low Carb &amp; Cholesterol</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/cholesterol/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:04:06 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:04:06 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/cholesterol/</guid>
        <description>Dr. Paul explains cholesterol, debunking the myth that high cholesterol is always bad Dr. Paul Mason
This is one of the best videos explaining cholesterol. Our medical professionals are perpetuating incorrect information propagated in the late 1950s by Ancel Keys who used selective world epidemiology studies to encourage the low fat diet. Cholesterol does not clog arteries, stating this is the equivalent of stating fireman start fires.
    Dr Paul Mason MD</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.comimages/posts/DrPaulMason.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Cholesterol</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Videos</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>USDA Guidelines; Fact or Fiction</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/usda-guidelines/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 07:54:52 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 07:54:52 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/usda-guidelines/</guid>
        <description>USDA not using acceptable scientific methodolgies for dietary recommendations. Dietary Guidelines 2015-20
The nation&amp;rsquo;s experts look at the best available science (or do they) to determine for the masses the best dietary practices for a healthy life. Their findings are found with facts, not conjecture, for they are the world&amp;rsquo;s experts. Is this how things really work? The Dietary Guideline for Americans (DGA) are all the proven facts? The decision makers in the DGA do not have any conflicts of interest, political bias, secret agendas?</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/USDA_Logo.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>USDA Guidelines</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Nutritional Confusion</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>We lost our minds to wheat</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/lost_our_minds/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 11:30:49 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 11:30:49 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/lost_our_minds/</guid>
        <description>We lost our minds to wheat This paper, purely hypothetical, but interesting none the less, by Stanton, J (2019)., published in the Journal of Evolution and Health, titled, Voices of the Gods: How we lost our minds to agriculture, purposes to explain our addiction to wheat and the effect wheat has on our minds. To get a better grasp of the author’s theory, I’d recommend visiting the wiki pages and read a few paragraphs on the subject of bicameralism physiology, at least look it up in Merriam-Webster.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/wheat.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Wheat Brain</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Nutritional Confusion</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Red Meat &amp; Oxidative Stress</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/red-meat-good/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/red-meat-good/</guid>
        <description>Interventional human study increased meat consumption With the exception of dairy products, animal sources of food are the least inflammatory products we consume. Animal products when properly raised and prepared also contain everything we need in the most bio available forms for full absorption. Humans have eaten animals for 2M-years, long enough to develop larger brains and smaller digestive systems.
Despite these facts, it amazes me when groups like WHO and LANCET declare something we’ve been eating for 2M-years a class 2 carcinogen.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/RedMeat.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Red Meat</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Soybeans and the Brain</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/soybean-oil/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/soybean-oil/</guid>
        <description>America&amp;rsquo;s most widely consumed oil. America&amp;rsquo;s most widely consumed oil causes genetic changes in the brain.
Most people think soybean oil is healthy regardless of it being highly processed. To extract oil from soybeans and other vegetables, producers use toxic chemicals. The chemicals are then removed, leaving us so called healthy unsaturated oils. Soy by itself is highly estrogenic. If you don’t know what estrogenic means, Google it. You can also look up the causes of man-boobs to learn about estorgenics.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/SoybeanOil.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Soybean oils</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Fiber is not necessarily beneficial for health</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/fiber/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/fiber/</guid>
        <description>Fiber is not necessary for good health; in fact, fiber can be detrimental to health. Carbohydrates are not a necessary nutrient for human health and fiber, both insoluble and soluble, are carbohydrates. There is no clinical data substantiating our health is dependent upon our intake of fiber. There is a clinical study in the publications section of this site discussing improved digestion when fiber is removed and Dr. Paul Saladino sums up the subject very well in the linked YouTube video.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/WholeGrain1.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Dietary Fiber</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Videos</category>
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Videos</category>
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Media misdirection</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/media/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/media/</guid>
        <description>Misleading CBC attack job Misleading CBC attack job portrayed as news to keep us healthy. This psychologist explains in detail that the advice given by CBC is misleading hyperbole. Research fats and find out what happens when polyunsaturated and unsaturated fats oxidize. We should not be eating the stuff.
https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/5-studies-on-saturated-fat
    </description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/CBC-hack.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Media Bias</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Oxidized Oils</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Videos</category>
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Nutritional Confusion</category>
            
          
            
              <category>Videos</category>
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Really, more fruits and vegetables?</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/more-fruits-and-vegetables/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/more-fruits-and-vegetables/</guid>
        <description>More fruits and vegetables really improve health? We’re consistently told, eating more fruits and vegetables reduces our risk of cardiovascular diseases. We’re also told these plant foods contain necessary antioxidants, vitamins and phytochemicals that ultimately improve our health. This guidance is solely based on observational studies, not randomized control studies. We’ll here is a control study published in the European Journal of Nutrition,
“Effect of increasing fruit and vegetable intake by dietary intervention on nutritional bio-markers and attitudes to dietary change: a randomized trial,” basically stating that increasing consumption of fruits and vegetables provides no signification health benefits or reduction in markers of disease.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/FruitsVeggies1.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Fruits &amp; Veggies</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Common Beliefs Revisited</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Published White Papers</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/papers/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 18:25:40 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 18:25:40 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/papers/</guid>
        <description>Interesting published papers Glycolytic control of vacuolar-type ATPase activity: A mechanism to regulate influenza viral infection
Hinissan P. Kohio, Amy L. Adamson (2013)
Description: The increase of viral infection via high glucose levels could be reversed by
, linking glucose metabolism and influenza viral infection.
University North Carolina
The Internal, External and Extended Microbiomes of Hominins
Robert R Dunn, Katherine R Amato, Elizabeth A Archie, Mimi Arandjelovic, Alyssa N Crittenden and Lauren M Nichols (2020)</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/paper.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Published Docs</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Resources</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Twitter Resources</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/twitter-follows/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 05:39:44 -0400</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 05:39:44 -0400</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/twitter-follows/</guid>
        <description>Twitter Resources    Name Twitter Address     Georgia Ede MD @GeorgiaEdeMD       Aseem Malhotra MD @DrAseemMalhotra       Gary Taubes @garytaubes       Gary Fettke MD @FructoseNo       Dr Eric Westman @drericwestman       Diet Doctor @DietDoctor       Andreas Eenfeldt MD @DrEenfeldt       Vinnie Tortorich @VinnieTortorich       Nina Telcholz @bigfatsurprise       Tim Noakes MD @ProfTimNoakes       Ted Naiman MD @tednaiman       Paul Saladino MD @CarnivoreMD       L Amber O’Hearn @KetoCarnivore       Shawn Baker MD @SbakerMD       Dave Asprey @bulletproofexec       Ken D Berry MD @KenDBerryMD       Jason Fung MD @drjasonfung       Benjamin Bikman PhD @BenBikmanPhD       Ivor Cummins @FatEmperor       Andreas Enfeldt MD @Dr.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Twitter</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Resources</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Books</title>
        <link>https://craigccfl.com/posts/books/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <atom:modified>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</atom:modified>
        <guid>https://craigccfl.com/posts/books/</guid>
        <description>* Life changing information for improving health.    Name Title (s)     Dr. Jason Fung: The Obesity Code *    The Diabetes Code *    The Complete Guide to Intermittent Fasting *    Life in the Fasting Lane       Dr. Ken Barry Lies My Doctor Told Me *       Dr.</description>
        
        <dc:creator>CraigW</dc:creator>
        <media:content url="https://craigccfl.com/images/posts/Books.png" medium="image"><media:title type="html">featured image</media:title></media:content>
        
        
        
          
            
              <category>Books</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
          
            
              <category>Resources</category>
            
          
            
          
        
        
      </item>
      

    
  </channel>
</rss>