<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Red Meat on Craigccfl</title>
    <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/tags/red-meat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Red Meat on Craigccfl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 13:07:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.craigccfl.com/tags/red-meat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Carnivore Eating</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/carivore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 13:07:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/carivore/</guid>
      <description>The ultimate way to eat zero carb. Most people end up on a carnivore diet by going through a process, they generally start out with Paleo then move to low-carb high-fat (LCHF) then many of us spend time doing the ketogenic diet. Usually, just out of curiosity, some of us move into a carnivore diet. IMO, it never hurts to try something for a couple months just to see how you feel (N=1).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meats Justified</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/tmao/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 11:24:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/tmao/</guid>
      <description>This is a technical paper for those who have delved into some of the scientific discussions regarding over activation of human growth hormone and its relationship with long-term health. The consensuses (beliefs) states over activation of metabolite trimethylamine-N-oxide (TMAO), creates excessive cellular oxidation leading to atherosclerosis, and diets high in choline (meat) cause over activation of TMAO. This is the science used by many who recommend limiting protein to an absolute minimum, usually 20% or less.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Meat &amp; Oxidative Stress</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/red-meat-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/red-meat-good/</guid>
      <description>With the exception of dairy products, animal sources of food are the least inflammatory products we consume. Animal products when properly raised and prepared also contain everything we need in the most bio available forms for full absorption. Humans have eaten animals for 2M-years, long enough to develop larger brains and smaller digestive systems.
Despite these facts, it amazes me when groups like WHO and LANCET declare something we’ve been eating for 2M-years a class 2 carcinogen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>