<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Videos on Craigccfl</title>
    <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/categories/videos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Videos on Craigccfl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 11:06:07 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.craigccfl.com/categories/videos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is eating chicken healthy?</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/reducingfats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 11:06:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/reducingfats/</guid>
      <description>Reducing saturated fats as suggested by our USDA, is very bad advice. They got it all wrong when they started promoting vegetable oils to replace saturated fats. Conventional wisdom suggests eating polyunsaturated fatty acid (PUFA) oils are healthier for our heart, despite interventional studies dating back to the 60s proving this advice is misleading. We consume more PUFAs today, yet the metabolic health of our society is rapidly declining each decade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven important reasons not to eat wheat</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/7reasons-wheat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 08:38:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/7reasons-wheat/</guid>
      <description>Eating whole grain breads to improve your health and increase fiber? Maybe it is not such a great idea. If it is processed food, it probably has wheat or a wheat by-product in the ingredients. Wheat is subsidized by our government, it&amp;rsquo;s cheap and very profitable for food companies. There&amp;rsquo;s many problems stemming from wheat products, detailed in the book Grain Brain (see books category). Dr Ken Berry has hundreds of YouTube videos posted online designed to help people improve their health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is salting our food bad for us?</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/salt_bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 10:59:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/salt_bad/</guid>
      <description>Salt is essential for life.
Our experts often advise us to restrict salt intake, based on what, faulty science? The answer to this question is yes, faulty science. Complications from insufficient salt intake are far worse than consuming excessive salt. The human body easily regulates excessive salt, with no side effects. The body cannot deal with a lack of salt in our systems. Low salt intake exacerbates insulin resistance, heart palpitations, dysfunctions in the nervous systems, headaches, increases hunger, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low carb &amp; keto what about cholesterol </title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/cholesterol2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 18:21:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/cholesterol2/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;ve Learned
This content creator puts out some good research pertaining to new science developments in the field of nutrition. Cholesterol is a hot topic, one of the major points of the nay sayers when discussing a diet low in carbs, high in saturated fats. Eating LCHF may increase your cholesterol; however, there&amp;rsquo;s much more to cholesterol than what we&amp;rsquo;ve been told. This video helps to put things into perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low Carb &amp; Cholesterol</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/cholesterol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:04:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/cholesterol/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Paul Mason
This is one of the best videos explaining cholesterol. Our medical professionals are perpetuating incorrect information propagated in the late 1950s by Ancel Keys who used selective world epidemiology studies to encourage the low fat diet. Cholesterol does not clog arteries, stating this is the equivalent of stating fireman start fires.
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiber is not necessarily beneficial for health</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/fiber/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/fiber/</guid>
      <description>Carbohydrates are not a necessary nutrient for human health and fiber, both insoluble and soluble, are carbohydrates. There is no clinical data substantiating our health is dependent upon our intake of fiber. There is a clinical study in the publications section of this site discussing improved digestion when fiber is removed and Dr. Paul Saladino sums up the subject very well in the linked YouTube video.
There’s several researchers and medical doctors that are not buying into the fiber crap, (pardon the pun).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media misdirection</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/media/</guid>
      <description>Misleading CBC attack job portrayed as news to keep us healthy. This psychologist explains in detail that the advice given by CBC is misleading hyperbole. Research fats and find out what happens when polyunsaturated and unsaturated fats oxidize. We should not be eating the stuff.
https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/5-studies-on-saturated-fat
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health and Nutrition YouTube Video Page</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/youtube-vids/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/post/youtube-vids/</guid>
      <description>Click on video to watch     Jon Venus &amp;amp; Paul Saladino MD
     Sustainable Ranching vs Mono Cropping
     Dr Paul Saladino Rob Wolf &amp;amp; Diana Rogers
     Dr Chris Knobbe
     Dr Paul Saladino
     Dr Harcombe
     Diet Doctor
     Dr Berry</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>