<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tubes on Craigccfl</title>
    <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tubes on Craigccfl</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 10:59:06 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is salting our food bad for us?</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/salt_bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 10:59:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/salt_bad/</guid>
      <description>Salt is essential for life.
Our experts often advise us to restrict salt intake, based on what, faulty science? The answer to this question is yes, faulty science. Complications from insufficient salt intake are far worse than consuming excessive salt. The human body easily regulates excessive salt, with no side effects. The body cannot deal with a lack of salt in our systems. Low salt intake exacerbates insulin resistance, heart palpitations, dysfunctions in the nervous systems, headaches, increases hunger, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low carb &amp; keto what about cholesterol </title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/cholesterol2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 18:21:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/cholesterol2/</guid>
      <description>What I&amp;rsquo;ve Learned
This content creator puts out some good research pertaining to new science developments in the field of nutrition. Cholesterol is a hot topic, one of the major points of the nay sayers when discussing a diet low in carbs, high in saturated fats. Eating LCHF may increase your cholesterol; however, there&amp;rsquo;s much more to cholesterol than what we&amp;rsquo;ve been told. This video helps to put things into perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Low Carb &amp; Cholesterol</title>
      <link>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/cholesterol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:04:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.craigccfl.com/tube/cholesterol/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Paul Mason
This is one of the best videos explaining cholesterol. Our medical professionals are perpetuating incorrect information propagated in the late 1950s by Ancel Keys who used selective world epidemiology studies to encourage the low fat diet. Cholesterol does not clog arteries, stating this is the equivalent of stating fireman start fires.
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>